# **SAKSHAM NAGAR**

### CONTACT



960-126-9846



sakshamnagar1996@gmail.com



sakshamnagar.github.io/resume



Ahmedabad, Gujrat

### **SKILLS**

- Django
- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

## **PROJECTS**

### (LINK IN CONTACT SECTION)

- Multi-Vendor e-commerce.
- College Project.
- Python Tic\_Tac\_Toe game
- Python BlackJack card game

### **LANGUAGE**

- English
- Hindi
- Gujrati

## **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

I am a fresher looking for exciting opportunities as Full Stack web developer or python software developer. I have 3+ years experience working in customer service and sales with some of the best organisations in Ahmedabad and Gandhinagar. I am dedicated and fast learner with good attention to detail..

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Internship: WayToWeb Pvt. Ltd. (January 2021 to April 2021)

- · Learnt about SDLC and production processes.
- Understood basics of Django and participated in Ecommerce project.
- Successfully built an ecommerce website using various languages.

# Online Chat Representative: Etech Global Services (October 2020 to June 2023)

- Participated in activities designed to improve customer satisfaction and sales performance.
- Ensured service delivered to our customers meets contractual sales goals and other Key Performance Indicators ('KPIs').
- Contribute ideas on ways to resolve problems to better serve the customer and/or improve productivity.
- Responsible for achieving specific sales business targets and maximising sales opportunities on each and every chat...

# Online Chat Representative: Etech Global Services (October 2020 to June 2023)

- Technical troubleshoot and gather information from customers to identify root causes of customer problems and/or dissatisfaction.
- Determine appropriate courses of action to ensure result is a win-win and documents interaction through contact tracking.
- Provide accurate product information and serving as a knowledgeable resource to customer..

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E) in Computer Science & Engineering (2022 passout)

SRI Group Of Institutions, Vadasma